var questions = [
    {
        question: "JavaScript is an __________ language.",
        choices: ["Object-Oriented", "Object-Based", "Procedural", "Markdown"],
        correct: 0
    },

    {
        question: "Which is used to define a variable in JavaScript?",
        choices: ["add", "var", "since", "None of the above"],
        correct: 1
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        choices: ["getElementbyId()", "getElementsByClassName()", "Both of the above", "None of the above"],
        correct: 2
    },

    {
        question: "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
        choices: ["in", "is in", "exists", "lies"],
        correct: 0
    },

    {
        question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        choices: ["parse()", "convert()", "serialize()", "stringify()"],
        correct: 3
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
        choices: ["Variables", "Functions", "Objects", "All of the above"],
        correct: 3
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a Javascript framework?",
        choices: ["React", "Bootstrap", "Vue", "Node"],
        correct: 1
    },

    {
        question: "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
        choices: ["async", "nosync", "desync", "syncless"],
        correct: 0
    },

    {
        question: "How do we write a comment in javascript?",
        choices: ["/* */", "//", "#", "<!-- -->"],
        correct: 1
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following are NOT server-side JavaScript objects?",
        choices: ["Date", "FileUpload", "Function", "All of the above"],
        correct: 3
    },
]

// Questions taken from or inspired by the quiz at https://www.interviewbit.com/javascript-mcq/